<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivolv</title>
    <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivolv</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dmishevchenko.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Advantage Ivolv</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/advantage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/advantage/</guid>
      <description>Home - Advantage Ivolv  Advantage Ivolv  Ivolv is an essential provider of bespoke artificial intelligence solutions, for global B2B companies, through targeted, customized and insightful data intelligence. We enable clients unlock value through our services by helping manage technologies efficiently, streamline systems &amp; processes to achieve optimum performances  We employ experts in data science and analysis, subject matter experts, and technology professionals. Besides, we draw in the expertise of our cross-functional teams as needed based on the project requirements and together we are committed to helping our customer progress in a growing digital world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Advantage Ivolv</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/advantage1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/advantage1/</guid>
      <description>Home - Advantage Ivolv  Advantage Ivolv  Ivolv is an essential provider of bespoke artificial intelligence solutions, for global B2B companies, through targeted, customized and insightful data intelligence. We enable clients unlock value through our services by helping manage technologies efficiently, streamline systems &amp; processes to achieve optimum performances  We employ experts in data science and analysis, subject matter experts, and technology professionals. Besides, we draw in the expertise of our cross-functional teams as needed based on the project requirements and together we are committed to helping our customer progress in a growing digital world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Banks</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/banks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/banks/</guid>
      <description>Industry - Banks &amp; finansial services   Banks &amp; finansial services  Banks and Financial Services firms have recognised their most valuable asset, data. They are keen to leverage the power of data for smarter, faster and accurate decisions. Big Data and analytics are creating unique opportunities of insight and innovation across the entire spectrum of financial services. Companies are able to provide unique customer experiences and secure access to their account data—anytime, anywhere, on any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Benefits</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/benefits/</guid>
      <description>Home - Benefits of Data Transformations   Benefits of Data Transformations  In the current customer-driven marketplace, CxOs are faced with a number of challenges – gaining a 360 degree view of the customer, widening the customer outreach across ever-increasing channels and marketing campaigns, lengthening the customer life-cycle, strengthening brand image, expanding business operations, as well as proving an effective ROI. Enterprise-wide transformation is being driven by an aggressive adoption of intuitive data-driven digital technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Digital</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/digital/</guid>
      <description>Home - Be a Part of the Digital Revolution   Be a Part of the Digital Revolution  Businesses are experiencing a big change in their ecosystem caused by an unprecedented digital revolution. Where IT systems and customer-facing processes are seamlessly connected in real-time, a business can survive only to the extent that it is in sync with the external environment.   Being sensitive to the evolving needs and perceptions of customers, understanding the changes occurring in technologies, improving and innovating product offerings, getting an early insight to the changes underway and knowing competition better; are increasingly becoming mandatory requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Empower</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/empower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/empower/</guid>
      <description>Home - Empower Your Journey from Data to Decisions  Empower Your Journey from Data to Decisions  Our data scientists at Ivolv Technologies are experts in data correlation and use of intramural frame-works. They work along with popular technologies to collect, cleanse, store, process and visualise data for timely decisions. Machine learning and predictive analytics are used to open up new opportunities in predictive data-driven decision making.   The Internet of Things and hyper mobility adoption, is transforming the way businesses function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Home</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>This is a data-driven digital world where changes aren’t linear; but exponential. The only way to survive is to keep pace with innovation and tie data to business growth.   Digital disruption is a great opportunity for business growth Make change happen, take advantage of the new opportunities that digital technology offers.  In today’s digital world, data is a driving force behind major business decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Industry Ivolv</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/industry/</guid>
      <description> Home - Industry Ivolv  Industry Banks &amp; Finansial Insurance  Travel Transportation &amp; Logistics     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Insurance</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/insurance/</guid>
      <description>Industry - Insurance   Insurance  Insurance companies are relying more and more on data for competitive advantage. Businesses are in a continuous state of flux, driven by unstable and transient economic and market factors. A constantly shifting regulatory climate and an unpredictable customer population, is driving uncertainties within the business. It is more important than ever that data-driven tools be used to factor uncertainties and risks, for devising premiums and designing policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Home - Automate Intelligence  Automate Intelligence   Businesses are undergoing a paradigm shift, as they realise the power of ‘data’. Data finds increased relevance in company policies and business decisions. It is paralleled as the “Renewed Energy” as it drives change in the way companies, market and influence customer behaviour. Like energy, data reaps huge rewards for companies who see its value and learn to extract and use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Transportation</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/transportation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/transportation/</guid>
      <description>Transportation &amp; logistics  Transportation &amp; logistics  The Transportation and Logistics Industry is served by various industry segments like airlines, airports, railways, cruising and freight logistics. What is common to all segments is the logistics management that ensures seamless delivery of assets and freight. Transportation and Logistics provides supply chain visibility across orders, shipments, and global inventories for operational efficiencies and savings. With increase in passenger traffic and an explosion of data and devices across a dynamic IoT network, the need for real-time or near real-time insights for timely decision making is critical to business performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Travel</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/travel/</guid>
      <description>Industry - Travel   Travel  The travel industry is data-intensive, with massive data generated at every touch point. From the moment a customer registers at an online booking portal, he creates a wealth of data – customer profile, travel preferences, flight paths, hotel bookings, destinations and more. When such information is combined with external data like social media, huge insights are obtained.   Ivolv creates a unified view of travel data for reporting, analysis and forecasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivolv :: Unleasing</title>
      <link>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/unleasing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dmishevchenko.github.io/unleasing/</guid>
      <description>Home - Unleashing the power of your data   Unleashing the power of your data  What’s the point in having vast data at your disposal if you cannot separate the chaff from the wheat?   Investing in your data is pointless unless you sift through the data maze and transform data into insights. For as customers become smarter and more informed, the marketplaces also evolve and become highly competitive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>